In this video, I'd like to
在这段视频中
tell you a bit about the
介绍一些
math behind large margin classification.
大间隔分类背后的数学原理
This video is optional, so please feel free to skip it.
本节为选学部分 你完全可以跳过它
It may also give you better
但是听听这节课可能让你对
intuition about how the
支持向量机中的优化问题
optimization problem of the
以及如何得到
support vex machine, how that
大间距分类器
leads to large margin classifiers.
产生更好的直观理解
In order to get started, let
首先
me first remind you of a
让我来给大家复习一下
couple of properties of what vector inner products look like.
关于向量内积的知识
Let's say I have two vectors
假设我有两个向量
U and V, that look like this.
u 和 v 我将它们写在这里
So both two dimensional vectors.
两个都是二维向量
Then let's see what U
我们看一下
transpose V looks like.
u 转置乘以 v 的结果
And U transpose V is
u 转置乘以 v
also called the inner products
也叫做向量 u 和 v
between the vectors U and V.
之间的内积
Use a two dimensional vector, so
由于是二维向量 我可以
I can on plot it on this figure.
将它们画在这个图上
So let's say
我们说
that's the vector U. And
这就是向量 u
what I mean by that is
即
if on the horizontal axis that
在横轴上
value takes whatever value
取值为某个u1
U1 is and on the
而在纵轴上
vertical axis the height
高度是
of that is whatever U2
某个 u2 作为U的
is the second component
第二个分量
of the vector U. Now, one
现在
quantity that will be nice
很容易计算的
to have is the norm
一个量就是向量 u 的
of the vector U. So, these
范数
are, you know, double bars on
这是双竖线
the left and right that denotes
左边一个 右边一个
the norm or length of
表示 u 的范数
U. So this just means; really the
即 u 的长度
euclidean length of the
即向量 u 的欧几里得长度
vector U. And this
根据
is Pythagoras theorem is just
毕达哥拉斯定理 等于
equal to U1
它等于 u1 平方
squared plus U2
加上 u2 平方
squared square root, right?
开根号
And this is the length of the vector U. That's a real number.
这是向量 u 的长度 它是一个实数
Just say you know, what is the length
现在你知道了
of this, what is the
这个的长度是多少
length of this vector down here.
这个向量的长度写在这里了
What is the length of this
我刚刚画的这个
arrow that I just drew, is the normal view?
向量的长度就知道了
Now let's go back and
现在让我们回头来看
look at the vector V because we want to compute the inner product.
向量v 因为我们想计算内积
So V will be some other
v 是另一个向量
vector with, you know,
它的两个分量 v1 和 v2
some value V1, V2.
是已知的
And so, the vector
向量 v
V will look like that, towards V like so.
可以画在这里
Now let's go back
现在让我们
and look at how to compute
来看看如何计算
the inner product between U
u 和 v 之间的内积
and V. Here's how you can do it.
这就是具体做法
Let me take the vector V and
我们将向量 v
project it down onto the
投影到
vector U. So I'm going
向量 u 上
to take a orthogonal projection or
我们做一个直角投影
a 90 degree projection, and project
或者说一个90度投影
it down onto U like so.
将其投影到 u 上
And what I'm going to do
接下来我度量
measure length of this
这条红线的
red line that I just drew here.
长度
So, I'm going to call the length of
我称这条红线的
that red line P. So, P
长度为 p 因此 p
is the length or is
就是长度 或者说是
the magnitude of the projection
向量 v 投影到
of the vector V onto the
向量 u 上的量
vector U. Let me just write that down.
我将它写下来
So, P is the length
p 是 v
of the projection of the
投影到
vector V onto the
向量 u 上的
vector U. And it is
长度
possible to show that unit
因此可以
product U transpose V, that
将 u 转置乘以 v
this is going to be equal
写作
to P  times the
p 乘以
norm or the length of
u 的范数或者说
the vector U. So, this
u的长度
is one way to compute the inner product.
这是计算内积的一种方法
And if you actually do
如果你从几何上
the geometry figure out what
画出 p 的值
P is and figure out what the norm of U is.
同时画出 u 的范数
This should give you the same
你也会同样地
way, the same answer as
计算出内积
the other way of computing unit product.
答案是一样的
Right.
对吧
Which is if you take U
另一个计算公式是
transpose V then U transposes
u 转置乘以 v 就是
this U1 U2, its a
[u1 u2] 这个一行两列的矩阵
one by two matrix, 1
乘以
times V. And so
v 因此
this should actually give you
可以得到
U1, V1 plus U2, V2.
u1×v1 加上 u2×v2
And so the theorem of
根据线性代数的知识
linear algebra that these two
这两个公式
formulas give you the same answer.
会给出同样的结果
And by the way, U transpose
顺便说一句
V is also equal to
u 转置乘以 v
V transpose U. So if
等于 v 转置乘以 u
you were to do the same process
因此如果你将 u 和 v 交换位置
in reverse, instead of projecting
将 u 投影到 v 上
V onto U, you could project
而不是将 v 投影到 u 上
U onto V. Then, you know, do
然后做同样地计算
the same process, but with the rows of U and V reversed.
只是把 u 和 v 的位置交换一下
And you would actually, you should
你事实上可以
actually get the same number whatever that number is.
得到同样的结果
And just to clarify what's
申明一点
going on in this equation the
在这个等式中
norm of U is a real
u 的范数是一个实数
number and P is also a real number.
p也是一个实数
And so U transpose V is
因此 u 转置乘以 v
the regular multiplication as two real numbers of
就是两个实数
the length of P times the normal view.
正常相乘
Just one last detail, which is
最后一点
if you look at the norm of
需要注意的就是p值
P, P is actually signed so to the right.
p事实上是有符号的
And it can either be positive or negative.
即它可能是正值 也可能是负值
So let me say what I mean
我的意思是说
by that, if U
如果 u
is a vector that looks like
是一个类似这样的向量
this and V is a vector that looks like this.
v 是一个类似这样的向量
So if the angle between U
u 和 v 之间的
and V is greater than ninety degrees.
夹角大于90度
Then if I project V onto
则如果将 v
U, what I get
投影到 u 上 会得到
is a projection it looks like
这样的一个投影
this and so that length
这是 p 的长度
P. And in this
在这个情形下
case, I will still have
我们仍然有
that U transpose V is
u 转置乘以 v
equal to P times the
是等于 p 乘以
norm of U. Except in
u 的范数
this example P will be negative.
唯一一点不同的是 p 在这里是负的
So, you know, in inner products if the angle
在内积计算中 如果 u 和 v 之间的夹角
between U and V is less
小于90度
than ninety degrees, then P
那么那条红线的长度
is the positive length for that red line
p 是正值
whereas if the angle of this
然而如果
angle of here is greater
这个夹角
than 90 degrees then P
大于90度 则p
here will be negative of
将会是负的
the length of the super line of that little line segment right over there.
就是这个小线段的长度是负的
So the inner product between two
因此两个向量之间的内积
vectors can also be negative
也是负的
if the angle between them is greater than 90 degrees.
如果它们之间的夹角大于90度
So that's how vector inner
这就是关于向量内积的知识
products work. We're going to
我们接下来将会
use these properties of vector
使用这些关于向量内积的
inner product to try
性质 试图来
to understand the support
理解支持向量机
vector machine optimization objective over there. Here
中的目标函数
is the optimization objective for the
这就是我们先前给出的
support vector machine that we worked out earlier. Just for
支持向量机模型中的目标函数
the purpose of this slide I
为了讲解方便
am going to make one simplification or
我做一点简化
once just to make the objective easy
仅仅是为了让目标函数
to analyze and what I'm going to do is
更容易被分析 我接下来忽略掉截距
ignore the indeceptrums. So, we'll just ignore theta 0 and set that to be equal to 0. To
令 θ0 等于 0
make things easier to plot, I'm also going to set N the number of features to be equal to 2. So, we have only 2 features,
这样更容易画示意图 我将特征数 n 置为2 因此我们仅有
X1 and X2.
两个特征 x1 和 x2
Now, let's look at the objective function.
现在 我们来看一下目标函数
The optimization objective of the
支持向量机的优化目标函数
SVM. What we have only two features.
当我们仅有两个特征
When N is equal to 2.
即 n=2 时
This can be written,
这个式子可以写作
one half of
二分之一
theta one squared plus theta two squared.
θ1 平方加上 θ2 平方
Because we only have two parameters, theta one and thetaa two.
我们只有两个参数 θ1 和θ2
What I'm going to do is rewrite this a bit.
接下来我重写一下
I'm going to write this as one
我将其重写成
half of theta one
二分之一 θ1 平方
squared plus theta two squared and
加上 θ2 平方
the square root squared.
开平方根后再平方
And the reason I can do that,
我这么做的根据是
is because for any number, you know, W, right, the
对于任何数 w
square roots of W and
w的平方根 再取平方
then squared, that's just equal
得到的就是
to W. So square roots
w 本身 因此平方根 然后平方
and squared should give you the same thing.
并不会改变值的大小
What you may notice is that
你可能注意到
this term inside is that's
括号里面的这一项
equal to the norm
是向量 θ
or the length of the
的范数
vector theta and what
或者说是向量 θ 的长度
I mean by that is that
我的意思是
if we write out the
如果我们将
vector theta like this, as
向量 θ 写出来
you know theta one, theta two.
θ1 θ2
Then this term that I've just
那么我刚刚画红线的这一项
underlined in red, that's exactly
就是向量 θ
the length, or the norm, of the vector theta.
的长度或范数
We are calling the definition
这里我们用的是之前
of the norm of the vector that we have on the previous line.
学过的向量范数的定义
And in fact this is actually
事实上这就
equal to the length of the
等于向量 θ
vector theta, whether you write
的长度
it as theta zero, theta 1, theta 2.
当然你可以将其写作  θ0 θ1 θ2
That is, if theta zero is equal to zero, as I assume here.
如果 θ0等于0
Or just the length of theta
那就是
1, theta 2; but for
θ1 θ2 的长度
this line I am going to ignore theta 0.
在这里我将忽略 θ0
So let me just, you know, treat theta
将 θ 仅仅写作这样
as this, let me just
这样来写 θ
write theta, the normal
θ 的范数
theta as this theta 1,
仅仅和 θ1 θ2 有关
theta 2 only, but the
但是
math works out either way,
数学上不管你是否包含 θ0
whether we include theta zero here or not.
其实并没有差别
So it's not going to matter for the rest of our derivation.
因此在我们接下来的推导中去掉θ0不会有影响
And so finally this means
这意味着
that my optimization objective is equal
我们的目标函数是
to one half of the
等于二分之一
norm of theta squared.
θ范数的平方
So all the support vector machine
因此支持向量机
is doing in the optimization
做的全部事情就是
objective is it's minimizing the
极小化参数向量 θ
squared norm of the square
范数的平方 或者说
length of the parameter vector theta.
长度的平方
Now what I'd like to do
现在我将要
is look at these terms, theta
看看这些项
transpose X and understand better what they're doing.
θ 转置乘以x 更深入地理解它们的含义
So given the parameter vector theta and given
给定参数向量θ 给定一个样本 x
and example x, what is this is equal to?
这等于什么呢?
And on the previous slide, we
在前一页幻灯片上
figured out what U transpose
我们画出了
V looks like, with different
在不同情形下
vectors U and V. And so we're
u转置乘以v的示意图
going to take those definitions, you know, with theta
我们将会使用这些概念
and X(i) playing the
θ 和 x(i) 就
roles of U and V.
类似于 u 和 v
And let's see what that picture looks like.
让我们看一下示意图
So, let's say I plot. Let's say I look at
我们考察一个
just a single training example. Let's say I
单一的训练样本
have a positive example the drawing
我有一个正样本在这里
was across there and let's say that is
用一个叉来表示这个样本
my example X(i), what
x(i)
that really means is
意思是 在
plotted on the horizontal axis
水平轴上
some value X(i) 1
取值为 x(i)1
and on the vertical axis
在竖直轴上
X(i) 2.
取值为 x(i)2
That's how I plot my training examples.
这就是我画出的训练样本
And although we haven't been really
尽管我没有将其
thinking of this as a vector, what
真的看做向量
this really is, this is a
它事实上
vector from the origin
就是一个
from 0, 0 out to
始于原点
the location of this training example.
终点位置在这个训练样本点的向量
And now let's say we have
现在 我们有
a parameter vector and
一个参数向量
I'm going to plot
我会将它也
that as vector, as well.
画成向量
What I mean by that is if I plot theta 1
我将 θ1 画在这里
here and theta 2 there
将 θ2 画在这里
so what is the inner
那么内积
product theta transpose X(i).
θ 转置乘以 x(i) 将会是什么呢
While using our earlier method,
使用我们之前的方法
the way we compute that is we
我们计算的方式就是
take my example and
我将训练样本
project it onto my parameter vector theta.
投影到参数向量 θ
And then I'm going to look
然后我来看一看
at the length of this segment
这个线段的长度
that I'm coloring in, in red.
我将它画成红色
And I'm going to
我将它称为
call that P superscript I
p 上标 (i)
to denote that this is a
用来表示这是
projection of the i-th training example
第 i 个训练样本
onto the parameter vector theta.
在参数向量 θ 上的投影
And so what we have is
根据我们之前幻灯片的内容
that theta transpose X(i) is
我们知道的是
equal to following what
θ 转置乘以 x(i)
we have on the previous slide, this
等于
is going to be equal to
就等于
P times the
p 乘以
length of the norm of the vector theta.
向量 θ 的长度 或 范数
And this is of course also equal to
这就等于
theta 1 x1
θ1 乘以 x1
plus theta 2 x2. So each
加上 θ2 x2
of these is, you know, an equally
这两种方式是等价的
valid way of computing the
都可以用来计算
inner product between theta and X(i).
θ 和 x(i) 之间的内积
Okay.
好
So where does this leave us?
这告诉了我们什么呢
What this means is that, this
这里表达的意思是
constrains that theta transpose X(i)
这个 θ 转置乘以 x(i)
be greater than or equal to one or less than minus one.
大于等于1 或者小于-1的
What this means is that it
约束是可以被
can replace the use of constraints
p(i)乘以x大于等于1
that P(i) times X
这个约束
be greater than or equal to one.
所代替的
Because theta transpose X(i) is
因为 θ 转置乘以  x(i)
equal to P(i) times the norm of theta.
等于 p(i) 乘以 θ 的范数
So writing that into our optimization objective.
将其写入我们的优化目标
This is what we get
我们将会得到
where I have, instead of
没有了约束
theta transpose X(i), I now
θ 转置乘以x(i)
have this P(i) times the norm of theta.
而变成了 p(i) 乘以 θ 的范数
And just to remind you we
需要提醒一点
worked out earlier too that
我们之前曾讲过
this optimization objective can be
这个优化目标函数可以
written as one half times
被写成二分之一乘以
the norm of theta squared.
θ 平方的范数
So, now let's consider
现在让我们考虑
the training example that we
下面这里的
have at the bottom and
训练样本
for now, continuing to use the simplification that
现在 继续使用之前的简化 即
theta 0 is equal to 0.
θ0 等于0
Let's see what decision boundary the support vector machine will choose.
我们来看一下支持向量机会选择什么样的决策界
Here's one option, let's say
这是一种选择
the support vector machine were to
我们假设支持向量机会
choose this decision boundary.
选择这个决策边界
This is not a very good choice because it has very small margins.
这不是一个非常好的选择 因为它的间距很小
This decision boundary comes very close to the training examples.
这个决策界离训练样本的距离很近
Let's see why the support vector machine will not do this.
我们来看一下为什么支持向量机不会选择它
For this choice of parameters
对于这样选择的参数 θ
it's possible to show that the
可以看到
parameter vector theta is actually
参数向量 θ 事实上
at 90 degrees to the decision boundary.
是和决策界是90度正交的
And so, that green decision boundary
因此这个绿色的决策界
corresponds to a parameter vector
对应着一个参数向量 θ
theta that points in that direction.
指向这个方向
And by the way, the simplification that
顺便提一句 θ0 等于0
theta 0 equals 0 that
的简化仅仅意味着
just means that the decision boundary
决策界必须
must pass through the origin, (0,0) over there.
通过原点 (0,0)
So now, let's
现在让我们看一下
look at what this implies
这对于优化目标函数
for the optimization objective.
意味着什么
Let's say that this example here.
比如这个样本
Let's say that's my first example, you know,
我们假设它是我的第一个样本
X1.
x(1)
If we look at the projection
如果我考察这个样本
of this example onto my parameters theta.
到参数 θ 的投影
That's the projection.
这就是投影
And so that little red line segment.
这个短的红线段
That is equal to P1.
就等于p(1)
And that is going to be pretty small, right.
它非常短 对么
And similarly, if this
类似地 这个样本
example here, if this happens
如果它恰好是
to be X2, that's my second example.
x(2) 是我的第二个训练样本
Then, if I look at the projection of this this example onto theta.
则它到 θ 的投影在这里
You know.
是因为你犯罪了 因为你做了错事
Then, let me draw this one in magenta.
我将它画成粉色
This little magenta line segment, that's
这个短的粉色线段
going to be P2. That's
它是 p(2)
the projection of the second example
第二个样本到
onto my, onto the direction
我的参数向量 θ
of my parameter vector theta which goes like this.
的投影
And so, this little
因此
projection line segment is getting pretty small.
这个投影非常短
P2 will actually be a negative number, right so P2 is
p(2) 事实上是一个负值
in the opposite direction.
p(2) 是在相反的方向
This vector has greater
这个向量
than 90 degree angle with my
和参数向量 θ 的夹角
parameter vector theta, it's going to be less than 0.
大于90度 p(2) 的值小于0
And so what we're finding is that
我们会发现
these terms P(i) are
这些 p(i)
going to be pretty small numbers.
将会是非常小的数
So if we look at
因此当我们考察
the optimization objective and see, well, for positive examples
优化目标函数的时候 对于正样本而言
we need P(i) times
我们需要 p(i) 乘以
the norm of theta to be bigger than either one.
θ 的范数大于等于1
But if P(i) over
但是如果 p(i) 在这里
here, if P1 over here
如果 p(1) 在这里
is pretty small, that means
非常小 那就意味着
that we need the norm of
我们需要 θ 的范数
theta to be pretty large, right? If
非常大 对么
P1 of theta is small
因为如果 p(1) 很小
and we want P1 you
而我们希望 p(1)
know times in all of theta
乘以 θ
to be bigger than either one, well
大于等于1
the only way for that
令其实现的
to be true for the profit that
唯一的办法就是
these two numbers to be large
这两个数较大
if P1 is small, as we
如果 p(1) 小
said we want the norm of theta to be large.
我们就希望 θ 的范数大
And similarly for our
类似地
negative example, we need P2
对于负样本而言 我们需要 p(2)
times the norm of
乘以
theta to be
θ 的范数
less than or equal to minus one.
小于等于-1
And we saw in this
我们已经在这个样本中
example already that P2
看到 p(2)
is going pretty small negative number,
会是一个非常小的数
and so the only way for
因此唯一的办法
that to happen as well is
就是
for the norm of theta to be
θ 的范数变大
large, but what
但是我们
we are doing in the optimization
的目标函数是
objective is we are
希望
trying to find a setting
找到一个参数 θ
of parameters where the norm
它的范数
of theta is small, and so
是小的
you know, so this doesn't
因此 这看起来
seem like such a good direction
不像是一个好的
for the parameter vector and theta.
参数向量 θ 的选择
In contrast, just look at a different decision boundary.
相反的 来看一个不同的决策边界
Here, let's say, this SVM chooses
比如说 支持向量机选择了
that decision boundary.
这个决策界
Now the is going to be very different.
现在状况会有很大不同
If that is the decision boundary,
如果这是决策界
here is the
这就是
corresponding direction for theta.
相对应的参数 θ 的方向
So, with the direction
因此 在这个
boundary you know, that
决策界之下
vertical line that corresponds
垂直线是决策界
to it is possible to
使用线性代数的知识
show using linear algebra that
可以说明
the way to get that green decision
这个绿色的决策界
boundary is have the vector of theta be
有一个垂直于它的
at 90 degrees to it,
向量 θ
and now if you look
现在如果你考察
at the projection of your
你的数据在横轴 x
data onto the vector
上的投影
x, lets say its before
比如 这个我之前提到的样本
this example is my example of x1. So when
我的样本 x(1)
I project this on to x,
当我将它投影到横轴x上
or onto theta, what I find is that this is P1.
或说投影到θ上 就会得到这样的p(1)
That length there is P1.
它的长度是 p(1)
The other example, that
另一个样本
example is and I
那个样本是x(2)
do the same projection and
我做同样的投影
what I find is that this
我会发现
length here is a
这是 p(2) 的长度
P2 really that is going to be less than 0.
它是负值
And you notice that now
你会注意到
P1 and P2, these lengths
现在 p(1) 和 p(2)
of the projections are going to
这些投影长度
be much bigger, and so
是长多了
if we still need to enforce
如果我们仍然要满足这些约束
these constraints that P1 of
p(1) 乘以 θ 的范数
the norm of theta is phase
是比1大的
number one because P1 is so much bigger now.
则因为 p(1) 变大了
The normal can be smaller.
θ 的范数就可以变小了
And so, what this means is
因此这意味着
that by choosing the decision
通过选择
boundary shown on the right
右边的决策界
instead of on the left, the
而不是左边的那个
SVM can make the
支持向量机可以
norm of the parameters theta
使参数 θ 的范数
much smaller. So, if we can
变小很多 因此如果我们想
make the norm of theta smaller and
令 θ 的范数变小
therefore make the squared norm of
从而令 θ 范数的平方
theta smaller, which is
变小 就能让
why the SVM
支持向量机
would choose this hypothesis on the right instead.
选择右边的决策界
And this is how
这就是
the SVM gives rise
支持向量机如何能
to this large margin certification effect.
有效地产生大间距分类的原因
Mainly, if you look
看这条绿线
at this green line, if you look at this green
这个绿色的决策界
hypothesis we want the
我们希望
projections of my positive
正样本和负样本投影到
and negative examples onto theta to be large, and
θ 的值大
the only way for that to
要做到这一点
hold true this is if surrounding the green line.
的唯一方式就是选择这条绿线做决策界
There's this large margin, there's
这是大间距决策界
this large gap that separates
来区分开
positive and negative examples is
正样本和负样本
really the magnitude of this gap.
这个间距的值
is exactly the values of
就是p(1) p(2) p(3)
P1, P2, P3 and so on.
等等的值
And so by making the margin
通过让间距变大
large, by these tyros P1,
通过这些p(1) p(2) p(3) 等等
P2, P3 and so on that's
的值 支持向量机
the SVM can end up with
最终可以找到
a smaller value for the
一个较小的 θ 范数
norm of theta which is what it is trying to do in the objective.
这正是支持向量机中最小化目标函数的目的
And this is why this
以上就是为什么
machine ends up with enlarge
支持向量机最终会找到
margin classifiers because itss
大间距分类器的原因
trying to maximize the norm
因为它试图极大化这些
of these P1 which is the distance from
p(i) 的范数 它们是
the training examples to the decision boundary.
训练样本到决策边界的距离
Finally, we did this whole derivation
最后一点 我们的推导
using this simplification that the
自始至终使用了这个简化假设
parameter theta 0 must be equal to 0.
就是参数 θ0 等于0
The effect of that as
就像我之前提到的
I mentioned briefly, is that if
这个的作用是
theta 0 is equal to
θ0 等于 0
0 what that means
的意思是
is that we are entertaining decision
我们让决策界
boundaries that pass through the
通过原点
origins of decision boundaries pass through
让决策界通过原点
the origin like that, if you
就像这样
allow theta zero to
如果你令
be non 0 then what
θ0 不是0的话
that means is that you entertain the
含义就是你希望
decision boundaries that did not
决策界不通过原点
cross through the origin, like that one I just drew.
比如这样
And I'm not going to do
我将不会做全部的推导
the full derivation that. It
实际上
turns out that this same
支持向量机产生大间距分类器的结论
large margin proof works in
会被证明同样成立
pretty much in exactly the same way.
证明方式是非常类似的
And there's a generalization of this
是我们刚刚做的
argument that we just went through
证明的推广
them long ago through that shows
之前视频中说过
that even when theta
即便 θ0
0 is non 0, what
不等于0
the SVM is trying to do when you have this optimization objective.
支持向量机要做的事情都是优化这个目标函数
Which again corresponds to the
对应着
case of when C is very large.
C值非常大的情况
But it is possible to
但是可以说明的是
show that, you know, when theta
即便 θ0 不等于 0
is not equal to 0 this
支持向量机
support vector machine is still
仍然会
finding is really trying
找到
to find the large margin
正样本和负样本之间的
separator that between the positive and negative
大间距分隔
examples. So that
总之
explains how this support vector machine is a large margin classifier.
我们解释了为什么支持向量机是一个大间距分类器
In the next video we
在下一节我们
will start to talk about how
将开始讨论
to take some of these
如何利用支持向量机的原理
SVM ideas and start to
应用它们
apply them to build a complex
建立一个复杂的
nonlinear classifiers.
非线性分类器 【教育无边界字幕组】翻译: shamolvzhou 校对/审核: 所罗门捷列夫